question_data = [
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Igneous rocks are formed by excessive heat and pressure.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Greenland is covered with grass and Iceland covered with ice.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The United States Department of Homeland Security was formed in response to the September 11th attacks.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy", "question": "No Game No Life first aired in 2014.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The 2005 video game &quot;Call of Duty 2: Big Red One&quot; is not available on PC.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "St. Louis is the capital of the US State Missouri.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The alternative rock band, They Might Be Giants, released their album &#039;Flood&#039; in 1990. ",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In Pok&eacute;mon, Arbok evolves into Seviper.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Tokyo is the capital of Japan.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Animals", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The internet browser Firefox is named after the Red Panda.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}

]
